<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<addon id="plugin.video.oneplayvip"
       version="0.2.8"
       name="[COLOR aquamarine][B]ONE[COLOR white]PLAY [COLOR aquamarine]VIP[/B][/COLOR]"
       provider-name="OnePlay">
    <requires>
        <import addon="xbmc.python" version="3.0.0"/>
        <import addon="script.module.requests"/>
        <import addon="script.module.urllib3"/>
        <import addon="inputstream.ffmpegdirect" optional="true"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="main.py">
        <provides>video</provides>
    </extension>
    <extension point="xbmc.service" library="service.py" start="startup"/>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
        <summary lang="en_GB">Xtream Codes client with Live TV, VOD, series, background EPG and global search.</summary>
        <summary lang="pt_BR">Cliente Xtream Codes com TV ao vivo, VOD, séries, EPG em background e busca global.</summary>
        <description lang="en_GB">Access live channels, films and series through Xtream Codes. The optional background EPG builds a local Today and Tomorrow guide. DNS and Live/VOD Proxy features are disabled by default and can be enabled individually when required. The Stable profile and extra tolerance help poor Xtream sources.</description>
        <description lang="pt_BR">Acesse canais ao vivo, filmes e séries pelo Xtream Codes. O EPG opcional em background monta uma guia local de Hoje e Amanhã. DNS e Proxy de Live/VOD começam desligados por padrão e podem ser ativados separadamente quando necessário. O perfil Estável e a tolerância extra ajudam fontes Xtream ruins.</description>
        <platform>all</platform>
        <license>GPL-2.0-or-later</license>
        <disclaimer lang="en_GB">A valid provider account is required. This add-on does not provide content. DNS and Proxy features are optional and disabled by default.</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="pt_BR">É necessário um acesso válido do provedor. Este addon não fornece conteúdo. DNS e Proxy são opcionais e começam desligados por padrão.</disclaimer>
        <assets>
            <icon>icon.png</icon>
            <fanart>fanart.jpg</fanart>
            <screenshot>resources/media/screenshot-1.jpg</screenshot>
            <screenshot>resources/media/screenshot-2.jpg</screenshot>
            <screenshot>resources/media/screenshot-3.jpg</screenshot>
        </assets>
    </extension>
</addon>